# Matthew J.S. Solano

Home: (909)823-1247 Cell: (909)329-5490

15059 Oak Spring dr 92336 Email: matthewsolano187@yahoo.com

# **OBJECTIVE**

To excel within a company that has room for advancement and competitive pay.

<u>SKILLS</u>		<b>LANGUAGES</b>	<b>PROGRAMS</b>
Management experience	Great people skills	C++	Adobe Creative Suite
Detail oriented	Excellent Multitasker	HTML	Maya
Hard worker	Fast Learner	JavaScript	Microsoft Office
Problem solver	Team Leader/ developer	Python	Pro Presenter
Great attitude	Guest service experience	CSS	Sound Track Pro

# **EXPERIENCE**

### Marketsource

Wireless Manager/Fontana, CA

8/2016-Current

Creating an excellent guest experience by maintaining a comfortable and professional environment, maximizing sales, teaching sales techniques, selling and educating guests about products and services with AT&T, Sprint, Verizon, and Direct TV.

#### Suncrest

Sales Area Manager/Ontario, CA

6/2016-8/2016

Driving sales by acquiring new customers for solar power management systems, delivering a high standard of customer service to current and future customers, obtaining and following through with appointments, giving presentations to breakdown personal sales analysis.

#### MTE Consulting

Lead Sales Rep/Rancho Cucamonga, CA

4/2016-6/2016

Acquired new customers for Frontier Communications, upgraded customer's lines, trained entry level reps in the systems and field, interviewed new prospects, managed my team for consistency in sales, set weekly goals for my team.

#### **Target**

Electronics Team Member/ Fontana, CA

8/2012 -4/2016

Organized and kept the store clean, driving sales, cashiered, stocked, customer service, ad setup & take down, promotions, electronics dept. knowledge, team lead, brand leader, guest service leader, price accuracy, backroom duties.

#### **Sycotic Conceptions**

Graphic artist /Riverside, CA

7/2011-8/2012

Graphics, labor, and delivery.

# **EDUCATION**

## Chaffey College / Rancho Cucamonga, CA

6/2015-2017

- Associates of Science in Computer Information Systems
- Associates of Arts in Business & Technology
- Associates of Arts in Arts & Humanities

## Fontana High School / Fontana, CA

9/2001-6/2005

Diploma